Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/profile-adas (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Data Analysis Quantitative Research Statistical Modeling

Languages

English (Full Professional)
Bengali (Native or Bilingual)
Hindi (Full Professional)

Patents

SYSTEM FOR CALCULATING COMPETITIVE INTERRELATIONSHIPS IN ITEM-PAIRS

Arunita Das

Data Scientist II at Amazon India Bengaluru

Summary

Data Science professional with 5 + years of experience. My current area of focus is unravelling consumer behaviour in retail/ ecommerce using the ever evolving suite of ML/statistical models and empowering the business by building such insight generating data science products.

Experience

Amazon India Data Scientist II September 2019 - Present (1 year) Bengaluru Area, India

@WalmartLabs India

4 years 1 month

Data Scientist May 2017 - September 2019 (2 years 5 months) bangalore

Statistical Analyst September 2015 - April 2017 (1 year 8 months)

Tata Consultancy Services
Sr. Business Analyst
July 2014 - August 2015 (1 year 2 months)
Electronic City, Bangalore

Joined the R&D team, Analytics and Insights ,TCS,Bangalore after completion of Masters Degree in Quantitative Economics. Role includes solving different business problems, building Demo Models enhancing capabilities of the team, providing end to end solutions to the valued clients in the field of analytics

Education

Indian Statistical Institute, Kolkata

Master's Degree, Econometrics and Quantitative Economics · (2012 - 2014)

Jadavpur University
Bachelor of Arts (B.A.), Economics · (2009 - 2011)